<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Dennis Dunkelmann - Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://ddunkelmann.github.io/portfolio/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Dennis Dunkelmann - Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ddunkelmann.github.io/portfolio/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mario Kart Setup Analysis</title>
      <link>https://ddunkelmann.github.io/portfolio/project/mariokart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ddunkelmann.github.io/portfolio/project/mariokart/</guid>
      <description>Background This analysis was made for a project within my friends, where each one gives a presentation on a topic of his or her choosing. The other participants have no background in statistics or data analysis, therefore my goal was to keep the analysis as understandable as possible without loosing interesting insights. I wanted to give my listeners something they keep after my presentation and can use for a specific purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Platform Webscraping</title>
      <link>https://ddunkelmann.github.io/portfolio/project/kk_scrape/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ddunkelmann.github.io/portfolio/project/kk_scrape/</guid>
      <description>Background This project was made for the release of the &amp;ldquo;The 50&amp;rdquo; Nike Dunk Off-White Collection. I wanted to analyze if certain colors in the 50 different colorways increased the overall value. I built this webscraping project to gather real world data from a german second-hand fashion marketplace.
Idea The overall plan was to get specific information about the product, mainly the price and colorway. Over the period of a month the script should scrape all of the new products since the last time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poker Data Collection Shiny</title>
      <link>https://ddunkelmann.github.io/portfolio/project/poker_shiny/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ddunkelmann.github.io/portfolio/project/poker_shiny/</guid>
      <description>Background This shiny application was built after my family and I joked about tracking our weekly poker games. We wondered if our comments after a session like Person X won so much today or we had a lot of flushs today would be close to the truth. This application is therefore designed, to allow me to track our games while we are playing.
You can find the application here.
Idea and Hypothesis The basic idea was to track information like who won, which hand did he win with, who played against him and how much money was bet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotify Top 100 2017 Analysis</title>
      <link>https://ddunkelmann.github.io/portfolio/project/spotify100/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ddunkelmann.github.io/portfolio/project/spotify100/</guid>
      <description>Background This project was a parallel training session during my university studies, to practice for my practical exam in the Intro Analytics Class. It was also my first time trying and working with Kaggle and a &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; non-test Dataset (like cars or diamonds).
Therefore this project was quite old and did not use all of the tricks and code practices I know at this point. I revisited it and rewrote most of the code and plots.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
